“I dreamed of being a musician when I was 15.”[w]
“I loved music, so much that I always used my spare time to make my own song,”[w]
“play my guitar and sing along…”[w]
“However, when I am older…”[w]

“......”[w]
“When did I have this head of a salted fish? I can hardly remember…”[w]
“......”[w]
“The road to work, every day, it is the same, the same scenery, over and over…”[w]
“The more I look at it, the more it looks like a looping picture…”[w]
“I have been on this path for years, yet, I still can’t get used to it….”[w]
“......”[w]
“Tch. I have been in the same position for years anyway.”[w]
“To be honest, at this point, I don’t think salary is a thing that can hold me back anymore,”[w]
“freaking bullshit.”[w]

“So…What should I do next??”[w] 【(a) Back to work，(b) Try other choices】
“Well, I’m kinda bored now. Maybe I should walk around and gossip.”[w]
