Looking up at the advertising wall, there is a poster of a student music competition. [w]
"A poster for a student music competition. It reminds me of my teenage years" [w]
"It seems so out of reach now... I mean, my air guitar skills are on point, but that's about it." [w] 
[(a) Tear it off, (b) Think about the past]
[Option a] "Do you want to throw it away?" [w]
[(a1) Throw it away, (a2) Keep it]
[Choosing (a1)] "Farewell, musical dreams!" [w]
[Choosing (a2)] "Ha...what on earth am I doing? Is this my hoarding tendencies kicking in again?" [w]
After staring at it for a few seconds, the poster was folded into a tetragon and stashed in the pocket. Fashion accessory upgrade! [w]
[Option b] "I have participated in this type of competition before."
"Although We didn't come back with the championship trophy, the time spent playing music with my lovely bandmates was a blast... literally, with all those power chords!" [w]
